Doctor summary (to see all details, run flutter doctor -v):
[!] Flutter (Channel stable, 3.41.2, on Microsoft Windows [Version 10.0.26200.7840], locale en-US)
    ! The flutter binary is not on your path. Consider adding C:\flutter\bin to your path.
    ! The dart binary is not on your path. Consider adding C:\flutter\bin to your path.
[ΓêÜ] Windows Version (Windows 11 or higher, 25H2, 2009)
[X] Android toolchain - develop for Android devices
    X Unable to locate Android SDK.
      Install Android Studio from: https://developer.android.com/studio/index.html
      On first launch it will assist you in installing the Android SDK components.
      (or visit https://flutter.dev/to/windows-android-setup for detailed instructions).
      If the Android SDK has been installed to a custom location, please use
      `flutter config --android-sdk` to update to that location.

[ΓêÜ] Chrome - develop for the web
[X] Visual Studio - develop Windows apps
    X Visual Studio not installed; this is necessary to develop Windows apps.
      Download at https://visualstudio.microsoft.com/downloads/.
      Please install the "Desktop development with C++" workload, including all of its default components
[ΓêÜ] Connected device (3 available)
[ΓêÜ] Network resources

! Doctor found issues in 3 categories.
